(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] February 12, 1988,
the dining staff aboard
this cruise liner
are making final preparations
ahead of tonight's
gala dinner service.
For one couple,
tonight's dinner
also marks the end of
a very special occasion
as 26-year-old Ashley and
new husband Charlie celebrate
the last night of their
honeymoon cruise to Costa Rica.
But unfortunately
for the new couple,
their happily ever after is
about to be cut tragically short
because later that
evening Ashley disappears.
(dramatic music)
What happened to Ashley?
Is it a terrible accident,
or is it a conspiracy
by secret government
agents to commit murder?
How did she end up dead?
(dramatic music)
(monitor beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
It's day one of the latest
voyage of this cruise ship.
(camera flashing)
At an incredible 635-feet long,
with many first-class amenities,
this ship is one of the most
beautiful vessels
in the world,
taking guests from California
down the Pacific Coast
to Costa Rica.
But unfortunately
for new bride, Ashley,
this week long cruise
through paradise
will be the last
trip of her life.
(dramatic music)
Ashley is celebrating
her honeymoon
with new husband, Charlie,
along with over 2500 guests,
crew members, and staff.
(people chatting)
But could one of them
be responsible
for her disappearance?
(camera flashing)
(people chatting)
(dramatic music)
Ashley grew up in Louisiana,
and is described by her
friends as a kindhearted
and soft spoken young woman.
But despite her
mild-mannered attitude,
years of modern dance, ballet,
and intense physical
fitness training
have sculpted her petite
five-foot four-inch frame
into that of a strong,
flexible athlete.
- I think since she was a
little girl she loved fitness.
She started out
actually with ballet,
and she went into
fitness classes
simply because she
was a very shy girl,
and she wanted to
bolster her confidence.
- [Narrator] After graduating
from massage therapy training
in Baton Rouge, Louisiana,
Ashley starts a career
as a massage therapist,
taking a position at a
Louisiana Country Club.
And it's here in June of 1988
that Ashley meets Charlie.
Charlie was born in Boston.
He meets Ashley
as a client first,
going in for some treatment
after falling down some stairs.
Ashley is immediately attracted
to her handsome muscular client,
who works as a
chiropractor in New Mexico.
- He's on her turf,
but they're both single,
they're both young,
they're both attractive.
It's the perfect opportunity
for something to happen.
- [Narrator] Ashley and
Charlie quickly realize
they have a lot in common,
including both of them
being passionate about
physical fitness.
For Charlie, his
fall down the stairs
means that falling in love
has a whole new meaning.
On February 4th,
Ashley and Charlie
drive his red
convertible to Las Vegas
and marry in a small
civil ceremony.
(people applauding)
- Well, Ashley was
still very young
when she decided
to marry Charlie,
and we were wanting
her to take more time.
But after a nine-month
whirlwind romance,
her heart was set,
so what could we say?
(gentle dramatic music)
- [Narrator] Two days later,
the Gerbers board a cruise ship
and start their seven-day
honeymoon cruise to Costa Rica.
(gentle dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
They're the perfect
all-American couple.
Beautiful and successful,
they even take the time to
exercise throughout the week.
Guests sit in
their lounge chairs
and watch them go through
their exercise routine.
(people chatting)
This couple seems destined
for a happy life together.
(dramatic music)
But at dinner on
February 12th,
guests notice some tension
between the picture-perfect
couple.
- On the last night
of the honeymoon
Charlie still wants
everything to be perfect.
He still wants them
to keep to their
perfect eating and
fitness routine.
Whereas, his wife
is a little more,
"Hey, let's live a little.
"It the last night
of our honeymoon."
(people chatting)
- [Narrator] Charlie
also isn't happy
about Ashley's
appetite for dessert.
- And that's when there
starts to be problems.
- [Narrator] Charlie's
outbursts gets the attention
of the other guests, including
some of the dining staff,
causing Ashley to run
out of the dining room
with tears in her eyes.
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
As Charlie chases after Ashley,
he gets into another argument
with a woman on the
deck of the boat.
When Charlie catches
up with Ashley
in their honeymoon cabin,
the lover's quarrel
doesn't last long.
- When couples
first get together,
there's that sort
of honeymoon phase,
and that may dissolve quickly
when small differences
in their personalities
start to show through.
- So it's the last night
of their honeymoon cruise,
and they decide, "Let's
blow off some tension.
"Let's reconnect to
the thing that bonds us
"and go for late-night
run on the track."
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] Eventually
Charlie's stops
to catch his breath,
but Ashley decides she wants
to get in a few more laps.
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
But unfortunately for Ashley,
this last lap will be the last
time anyone sees her alive.
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
Later that night,
Charlie bursts into
the Captain's quarters
with horrific news.
His wife has gone overboard.
(muffled voice speaking
on radio)
(dramatic music)
Ashley and Charlie seem to be
the perfect all-American couple.
After a whirlwind
romance and marriage,
the pair have set sail
on a cruise ship to enjoy
a week long honeymoon voyage
down the Pacific Coast.
- My husband and I felt that
she would do things
spontaneously,
and even getting married
was one of those things.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] But after an
argument in the dining hall,
Charlie can't help but notice
the other guests watching them,
especially his
beautiful wife, Ashley.
(dramatic music)
But after a late-night jog
on the last night of their
cruise, Ashley disappears.
Is it possible there's
a killer on board?
At 3:00 a.m. on
February the 13th,
the cruise ship's
Captain is interrupted
by a frantic Charlie, who
says that his wife Ashley
has gone overboard.
(muffled voice speaking
on radio)
The ship's crew use flashlights
to search for
Ashley in the water.
(suspenseful music)
Charlie is still wearing his
running gear and out of breath.
But the Captain also notices
Charlie has injuries
on his face.
- We're investigating
a potential homicide.
So when one of the
parties involved
shows up with wounds to
their face scratches, cuts,
it can indicate that there
was some sort of struggle,
some sort of
physical altercation
that resulted in those injuries.
- [Narrator] But
before the Captain
can ask how Ashley
went overboard,
Charlie asks to
use the restroom.
(dramatic music)
When Charlie goes
into the restroom,
the Captain can see him checking
out and washing his face.
- It's certainly unusual
that you would want
to clean a scratch on your
face before anything else.
- [Narrator] Now with
his face cleaned up,
Charlie is ready to explain
how Ashley went overboard.
(dramatic music)
Charlie tells the Captain
that the two of them
had gone for a late-night
run around the ship.
But then tragically,
Charlie says that the wind
starts to pick up
and get stronger.
So strong that it pushes Ashley
over the edge of the ship.
She tries her best to hang on,
but the ocean winds
are too much...
(dramatic music)
Sending her plummeting
into the ocean below.
Next, the Captain asks about
the cuts on Charlie's face.
Charlie says that when he
heard Ashley's screams,
he tried to save her,
but the winds were too strong
and sent him flying into a wall
causing him to hit his
face on a control box.
- Well, when you're
on a cruise ship,
you're still at the
mercy of elements,
flash storms, high
winds, violent waves.
If the winds got high
enough and strong enough,
someone might've
been blown overboard.
(dramatic music)
(water splashing)
- [Narrator] Unfortunately,
despite an exhaustive search,
the crew can't locate
Ashley's body in the water,
which means unless
there's any witnesses,
the last person to see
Ashley alive was Charlie.
(gentle music)
But while there's no
evidence of any foul play,
the Captain can't help but feel
like Charlie's story
isn't adding up.
- There's holes in
Charlie's story though.
The Captain looks at
the weather that night,
and the wind speeds for
only five miles an hour.
That's nowhere near enough
to blow someone overboard.
Seas were fairly calm.
They weren't that
rough that night.
So already there's
some suspicion
building about this guy's story.
- [Narrator] All of this
makes the Captain wonder
if there's more to
Charlie's story.
- In this particular case,
the winds were
only reported to be
in the range of
five miles an hour,
which is barely enough
to ruffle your hair.
- [Narrator] Is it possible
thatsomeone else
could have murdered, and
Charlie covered it up?
(dramatic music)
After the Captain
calls to notify police
and the Coast Guard of the
ship's overboard situation,
he calls in the ship's
medical officer Dr. Price
to examine Charlie's injuries,
which proved to be superficial.
(dramatic music)
But then, the Captain
informs Charlie,
that the doctor is also
deputized as a law officer
and would like to interview
Charlie officially
to take down the details
of what happened.
- If the ship is at sea,
the Captain would need
to deputize somebody
or would have a security
officer on board
who would be
responsible for looking
after serious
incidents like this.
- [Narrator] Charlie is
willing to be cooperative
and agrees to let the doctor
record their conversations
and answer his questions
as best as he can.
- Timelines are
incredibly important
when we're talking
about any serious crime,
particularly homicide.
(people chatting)
Everything leading up to that
event needs to be documented.
It needs to be questioned.
Who was involved?
Who was around?
Where did things take place,
and what happened
immediately after it?
(tense music)
- [Narrator] While
Charlie sits across
from the doctor to
give his statement,
the Coast Guard begins their
search for Ashley's body.
The question the doctor
wants to answer is
if it's possible
that Ashley's death
was more than just
a freak accident?
His investigation will
take him all over the ship,
forcing him to ask a
terrifying question.
Is it possible that the
ship has a murderer onboard?
(suspenseful music)
(water sloshing)
All eyes around the fitness
inspired Ashley and Charlie,
(camera flashing)
who are celebrating
their honeymoon
with a seven-day voyage
down the Pacific Coast
on a beautiful cruise ship.
But as the cruise winds down,
some people have noticed
the once happy couple
aren't so happy.
(dramatic music)
But after a late-night
running session
ends with Ashley
going overboard,
husband Charlie is
forced to sit down
with the ship's medical doctor
and a deputized law officer
to explain what happened.
(dramatic music)
Charlie says he's willing
to be fully cooperative
and answer any questions
the doctor might have.
He also gives Dr. Price
permission
to keep the cabin door open
and to record audio
of their discussion.
Charlie tells his version
of what happened
earlier that morning.
He sticks to his original story
of how Ashley was out
for a late-night jog,
only to be blown
overboard by strong winds.
(dramatic music)
But as the Captain
noted earlier,
the wind speeds at the time
were only around
five miles per hour.
That wouldn't be
enough to blow any
full grown adult
over the railings,
which are three-foot,
six-inches high,
especially someone with
Ashley's athletic background.
The doctor isn't
buying Charlie's story.
But with no evidence
of his involvement
in a potential murder,
he places Charlie in
an unoccupied cabin
under protective guard while
he continues his investigation.
(gentle dramatic music)
Meanwhile, the Coast Guard
continues searching
the open waters
for Ashley's body.
Then, as the ship continues
to its destination,
the doctor and the
Captain get a lead
from one of their passengers.
The man turns out to be
an off-duty police officer
and has found what appears to
be one of Ashley's earrings
embedded in the running track
near where she went overboard.
What's more, he's also
found a few strands
of Ashley's hair stuck
to the running track.
(suspenseful music)
- Protections need
to be put in place
to preserve whatever
evidence may be there
to show whether
it's a crime or not.
So everything needs to
be treated as a homicide
right from the beginning
until you learn it's not.
- [Narrator] With
this new evidence
showing signs of a
possible struggle,
the doctor decides to try
and verify Charlie's claim
that the scratches on his
face were from hitting
a control box during his
attempt to save Ashley.
But upon further inspection,
the doctor can't find any
of Charlie's blood, hair,
or other marks on
the control box.
In fact, it appears to
have no sharp edges at all,
which makes the doctor wonder
if Charlie could be lying
about the source
of his injuries.
- It's one of the
biggest challenges
faced by the
investigators in this case
was there was no
other witnesses.
It was three o'clock
in the morning.
Everyone else was asleep.
So they only have Charlie's word
about what happened
to Ashley.
No one else saw
what was happening.
They were all fast
asleep in their cabins.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] The
doctor decides instead
to question some of
the guests to see
if they saw anything suspicious
between Ashley and Charlie
during their trip and before
Ashley's disappearance.
- But there was something
people witnessed.
There was conflict
on that last night,
and everyone around
them witnessed
a fight at the dinner
table that night.
(people chatting)
So we do have that.
We do have that there
was some friction
between them the night she died.
And there are
witnesses who saw that
and could talk about it.
And there was also another
argument, an altercation,
that Charlie had with
a female passenger
that evening as well, so...
That could show where
his mood was that night.
Maybe he was already really
angry about something
or just a bit off that day.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] With his
less than stellar alibi,
combined with the
witness testimony,
the doctor is starting to wonder
if Charlie himself
could be responsible
for his wife's disappearance.
But why would what looked
like an innocent argument
send a husband to potentially
murder his new wife
on their honeymoon?
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
But then Dr. Price
gets a surprise visit
from another passenger, Rachel,
who claims to have
witnessed Ashley
being followed by a man the
night of her disappearance.
- But as it turns out, Charlie's
not the only strange man
on board that day.
There's another fellow.
A woman named
Rachel comes forward
and tells the police that
she was approached by a man
that gave her the creeps
the first day on the cruise.
- [Narrator] This strange
man pressures Rachel
into accepting a drink
from him, but she refuses.
- When she managed to
blow him off and get away,
who does he hit on, but Ashley.
This guy's really memorable too.
He's so sunburned that
Rachel describes him
as looking like a
bright red tomato.
(dramatic music)
(people chatting)
So one thing Rachel observes
is that the sunburned guy
is almost stalking Ashley
during her time on the
cruise ship, which is weird.
Makes Rachel really glad she
didn't accept that drink.
- [Narrator] Unfortunately,
Rachel doesn't know
the man's last name,
but says the doctor will be able
to recognize him
because of his sunburn.
The doctor thanks Rachel
for the new information,
and adds Eric to his list
of possible suspects.
This makes two people who
would have seen Ashley
after she left the dining hall.
(dramatic music)
But with still no witnesses
for the moment she
went overboard,
Dr. Price can't help but
wonder what if someone else
is responsible for
Ashley's disappearance.
(people chatting)
Suddenly, after
hours of searching,
the Coast Guard has tragically
found Ashley's body.
(water sloshing)
What's more, they've confirmed
this case is a cold
blooded murder,
which means the killer
is still on board.
(suspenseful music)
Ashley and Charlie are
celebrating their honeymoon
with a seven-day voyage on
a beautiful cruise ship,
but some of their
daily exercise routines
have caught the eyes of
some other passengers.
But during a late-night
running session,
Ashley is mysteriously
thrown overboard
resulting in one of her earrings
and strands of hair being
found on the ship's deck.
(dramatic music)
Ashley's husband Charlie
tells the ship's doctor,
the de facto investigator,
that his wife lost her balance
after heavy winds blew
her over the edge.
But the doctor
knows that the winds
were only five miles
per hour that night,
which aren't strong enough
to move a grown woman.
Meanwhile, another
witness claims
to have allegedly seen
Ashley being followed
by a sunburned man the
night she went missing.
(suspenseful music)
Then, after nearly 10
hours of searching,
the Coast Guard
spots Ashley's body.
- So even though the
ocean is huge and vast,
luckily Ashley's clothes
kept enough air inside
that her body stayed buoyant,
and the Coast Guard was
able to discover her.
- [Narrator] For police
this is a sign that Ashley
was either unconscious
or already dead
when she landed in the water.
As the medical examiner
inspects Ashley's body,
they find multiple examples
of physical injuries
sustained before she
was dumped overboard.
- There is something
about knowing
that your daughter
is never coming back,
and there is knowing
that she's been found.
- [Narrator] The medical
examiner finds a goose egg
type bump on Ashley's forehead
suggesting she was hit
with either a fist
or a blunt object.
(dramatic music)
They also find marks
on her neck along with
signs of hemorrhaging
in her neck and eyes,
which all point to
manual strangulation.
Ashley's clothing also
contained material
from the jogging
track on the deck,
which means she was
being pressed down
with considerable force,
potentially from someone
on top of her.
- What would bruising around
a person's neck indicate
in a medical examiner's report?
It would tell me
it was a homicide.
- [Narrator] With confirmation
from the medical examiner,
Dr. Price and staff
aboard the ship
can officially confirm they
have a murderer on board.
The questions now are who
killed Ashley and why?
(dramatic music)
- I can't even imagine her
not being in our life anymore.
- So because Charlie's been
kept in quarantine all this time
when the news breaks
that this investigation
has turned into a
murder investigation,
and there's something suspicious
with his wife's death,
he's in the dark.
He has no idea.
- [Narrator] With only
a couple hours remaining
before the cruise ship
reaches its final destination
for police to take over,
the doctor decides it's time
to question his second suspect.
Eric, the sunburned man,
who was spotted following
Ashley the night of her murder.
(dramatic music)
Eric is a Wisconsin
born accountant
who tells the doctor
that he decided
to take a cruise as a
way to meet single women,
but when the doctor confronts
him about being spotted
following Ashley around
the ship, Eric denies it.
When the doctor tells Eric
that Ashley has been murdered
and that he's a
potential suspect,
Eric immediately comes clean.
- Eric, once he hears that
he's a suspect, realizes that
being embarrassed is way
better than doing prison time.
So he comes forward
to the investigators,
and admits that sure,
he had a crush on Ashley,
and maybe he followed
her around too much.
He feels really badly about
that, but he has an alibi.
He had nothing to
do with her murder.
- [Narrator] Unfortunately
for Eric, his attempt
to romance the tearful
newlywed doesn't go as planned.
- It was embarrassing for
Eric to admit that Ashley
even got angry with how
he was hovering over her
and following her around.
Once she told him to leave
her alone, he did back off.
(dramatic music)
He went to the bar that
night, got stinking drunk,
and then was in his
berth throwing up
for the rest of his night.
(Eric coughing)
The brother heard
and had to take care of him.
So if his brother can
also verify his alibi.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] While
Dr. Price is happy
to cross Eric off the list,
he warns him against
approaching any women
for the remainder of the cruise
telling him to stay in his
room and out of the sun.
(dramatic music)
Which leaves only one
remaining suspect.
- When Ashley's body is examined
by the medical examiner,
they discover that she still
has her engagement ring on,
and its dimensions match the
scratches on Charlie's face.
So that's pretty
damning evidence.
(suspenseful music)
- [Narrator] For the
doctor this final clue
is the last piece
of evidence he needs
to confirm his suspicions.
On February 15, 1988,
the ship reaches the port
of Long Beach, California.
Police are waiting
to arrest Charlie
for the murder of
his wife, Ashley.
He's held without
bail until trial.
- With such a strong
case against him,
Charlie seems destined
for life in prison,
but after only
three days in jail,
he comes to a
sudden realization.
- [Narrator] Charlie demands
to speak with his lawyer.
Charlie says he was framed
for his wife's death,
and what's more, he
knows who did it.
(people chatting)
On the outside Ashley
and Charlie appear to be
the perfect all-American couple,
combining their seven-day
honeymoon cruise
with eye-catching
exercise routines.
Until tragically the
honeymoon is cut short
when Ashley's body
is found in the ocean
after being strangled
and dumped overboard.
Charlie denies his involvement,
but with strong
evidence against him
and without a credible alibi,
he's arrested for
Ashley's murder.
But after three days in jail,
Charlie calls his lawyer
with some startling
new information.
He says not only has he been
framed for his wife's murder,
he's figured out
who did it and why.
(dramatic music)
- There were these two
suspicious looking Ukrainian men
that were on the ship at
the same time as Charlie,
and he's convinced
that they're the ones
responsible for
his wife's murder.
- [Narrator] Charlie tells
his lawyer that he believes
Ashley's murder traces
back to a government
conspiracy that began
almost 11 years earlier.
- In 1978, Charlie
traveled to Ukraine
with his parents to open
a chiropractic clinic.
This should be a new
beginning for the family.
It should be a wonderful time,
but somehow Charlie
ended up in jail
and a mental hospital
for two months.
While he's there,
he's allegedly
drugged and beaten
because he refuses to
marry a neighbor's niece.
(dramatic music)
After he finally manages
to get back to the U.S.,
he writes a book
about his experiences
and all the horror that
happened to him there.
- So one of the things that
he said during the case
was that the Ukraine
government was after him.
(dramatic music)
- So around the time
the book is published,
the police contact Charlie's
parents with reports
that someone has a
plot to kidnap Charlie
outside a shopping mall.
Charlie claimed that
two men grabbed him
and said, "Ukraine is
here to take you away."
But somehow Charlie manages
to break free and escape,
even shooting one of
the would-be kidnappers.
As he makes his bid for freedom,
he then runs to his
car and drives away.
Charlie's eventually quoted
in a newspaper saying,
"All of Ukraine took their
best shot and they blew it."
This is why he believes
that the two men
on the ship were actually
Ukrainian government agents
who are there to
retaliate against him
for writing this book,
and that's why they
murdered his wife.
- [Narrator]
According to Charlie,
him and Ashley are exercising
on the running track
when his wife is
viciously attacked
by a stranger and
his accomplice.
(suspenseful music)
- As a writer, a
writer of fiction,
I have a hard time
with this story.
It seems a little
too good to be true,
and this is such a great story,
these Ukrainian government
agents, perfect story.
So why did Charlie
first have that yarn
about his wife being
blown over the rail?
Why not tell the truth
from the beginning?
But Charlie of
course has a theory.
Of course, he must
have been drugged.
That's why he thought he saw
his wife blown over the edge.
It was because he was drugged.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] It's an incredible
story, and if it's true,
it'll all come out
during Charlie's trial.
(dramatic music)
The prosecution outlines
a straightforward case
against Charlie, first by
using the forensic evidence
provided by the
medical examiner,
as well as testimony
from the cruise ship crew
and passengers who witnessed
the couple arguing.
(people chatting)
But Charlie maintains
his innocence,
resting his entire defense on
the idea of him being framed
by the Ukrainian passengers.
But the prosecution
surprises everyone
when they bring one of the
Ukrainian men to the stand.
- It turns out there's
only two Ukrainian people
on this entire cruise ship,
and one of them decides to
testify to clear his name.
He's not a secret agent.
He's got no connection
to the government.
He's just a wedding photographer
who is there for a
vacation with his friend.
The story of the photographers
is definitely true.
They were photographers
just there
to take a picture of a wedding,
and it was a friend's wedding.
- [Narrator] The prosecution
closes their case
by outlining exactly
how they believe Charlie
killed his wife Ashley.
(dramatic music)
It all starts with a bad
argument over dinner,
the couple tries to
put it behind them,
but during a late-night jog,
Charlie's rage boils over.
(ominous music)
First, Charlie hits
Ashley in the head,
knocking her earring off,
sending her crashing
to the deck.
Then he climbs on top
of her and strangles her
pushing her down
into the ship's deck
and holding her until
she's unconscious.
Then Charlie carries her
body to the rail of the ship
and tosses her overboard
(water sloshing)
while she's still unconscious.
Her official cause of
death is listed as drowning
by way of manual strangulation.
(dramatic music)
- Even with all the
evidence against him,
Charlie sticks with
his Ukrainian story.
He tells the jury
that even though
his story may seem contrived,
these things do happen
in the world of
international intrigue.
- [Narrator] Is it possible
that Ashley's murder
is part of a targeted Ukrainian
government conspiracy,
or was Ashley's
death nothing more
than a tragic
cold-blooded murder?
It will be up to
the jury to decide.
(dramatic music)
Charlie is on trial for the
murder of his wife Ashley.
He's accused of murdering
her on their honeymoon.
The prosecution has a solid case
backed up by medical evidence
and witness testimony,
but Charlie says he's been
framed for the murder.
He claims that his wife's death
is in fact a retaliation
by the Ukrainian government
for a book he wrote about
them a year earlier.
With both arguments presented,
all that's left is for
the jury to determine
if they believe in
Charlie's Ukrainian
government retaliation
killing theory,
or that he's the murderer,
willing to say whatever he
can to stay out of jail.
(dramatic music)
- So Charlie's
got a big problem.
His story is full of holes,
and everything'S
just not adding up.
There's so much against him.
People saw him arguing with
his wife the night she died.
The forensic evidence,
scratches on his face,
the fact that there's signs
that she was strangled,
the alibi that the
Ukrainians had,
so they couldn't possibly
be the ones that drugged him
and threw his wife overboard.
All of this is
pointing to Charlie.
- [Narrator] Charlie Gerber's
espionage defense
is not enough to
sway the jury,
who find him guilty of
second degree murder
on the high seas.
(people chatting)
- In the end the judge said
he'd never seen a honeymoon
that ended in such a chilling
and heartless manner.
He called Ashley's murder
one of the cruelest
crimes he'd ever seen.
- Your daughter
can never come back,
but to do have closure
in knowing that
Charlie was arrested
and convicted.
- [Narrator] Charlie is
sentenced to life in prison
without parole for the
murder of his wife Ashley.
It's a senseless and tragic
end to what should have been
a beautiful start to a
beautiful life together.
(people applauding)
(dramatic music)
(water sloshing)